<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Engels on GIP Bert Gysen</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/engels/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Engels on GIP Bert Gysen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 May 2016 00:12:25 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/engels/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Review of software Kaseya</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Taak/IT-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2016 00:12:25 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Taak/IT-review/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;kaseya-review:b2c60582955df1dde12efefda9c3a93d&#34;&gt;Kaseya review&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kaseya is a networking tool used by system administrators to make their life a bit easier. The tool is created by the company Kaseya and contains several functions like remote control, monitoring, dashboards, patch management and so on. The company that uses the tool pays a monthly fee based on the number of clients and servers in that company. My first encounter with Kaseya happened at my training company where my mentor used it to monitor everyone working there. He could also help people but that didn’t happen very often.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main feature of Kaseya which can be viewed both as a positive and a negative thing is that it runs in a browser. That means that you need to have internet connection to access it. An advantage of having the tool running in a browser is that you can access it from any place. If something goes wrong in the network and you are at home you can easily connect to Kaseya and fix it without having to go to the company. The downside of needing internet connection for Kaseya is that when your internet connection is down you are not able to access the tool anymore. I personally think that running the tool in a browser is not a good idea. I think that while being able to access the tool wherever you are is a really good thing, Kaseya also needs an option to run without the need of a browser in case there are problems with the connection.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To include a client in the tool you need to install the Kaseya agent on that client. Once a client has the agent installed the system administrator can shut down processes, take control of the client, install things and much more. A drawback of the agent is that you need to install it on every single client in your company, which can take a long time. Also, if the user has the rights he can uninstall the agent, therefore the client will be removed from the tool. As long as you don’t give the rights to uninstall there won’t be any problems with the agent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing that the tool succeeds in is having regular updates. Once every few weeks the tool gets an update that takes care of bugs and other problems. It also adds new features. The updates are free for everyone who pays monthly for the tool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;../../Kaseya1.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IT-tapa instructie video</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Taak/InstructionVidEnglish/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2015 00:14:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Taak/InstructionVidEnglish/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;trello-tutorials:5d7ee15a3e86b02505ae15f9d053a490&#34;&gt;Trello Tutorials&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nederlands filmpje: &lt;br&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&#34;75%&#34; height=&#34;330&#34; src=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/embed/vtrBZNaJU_c&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Engels filmpje: &lt;br&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&#34;75%&#34; height=&#34;330&#34; src=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/embed/cej_UYiT3Mk&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IT-autobiography</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Taak/IT-autobiography/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2015 00:12:25 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Taak/IT-autobiography/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-it-became-a-part-of-my-life:b8ba8b1fcf0c24f1bbf715390a897859&#34;&gt;How IT became a part of my life&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My name is Bert Gysen. I’m a 17-year old programming champion who does IT management at the Immaculata Institute. I have loved programming ever since I first got in touch with it and I’m going to tell you how IT has become a part of my everyday life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My first experience with IT occurred when I was 6 years old. I was playing at a friend’s house when he decided to play a game on his computer. I was fascinated by all that he could do. He was jumping and fighting enemies. I had never seen something like that. In those days I just watched television all the time. My aunt had a computer as well so I loved to visit her. I didn’t even have a computer back then, so a few months later I got one too, back then I always went to funnygames.com or spele.nl to play games. In my fourth year of high school I hadn’t planned to do IT management but when we started basic programming I immediately knew I wanted to do this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nowadays my computer is part of my everyday life.  When I come home the first thing I do is turn on my computer and check Facebook. I’m on my computer all the time, easily 5 hours a day. Sometimes when I’m bored I start programming something new. I love the creative aspect of programming and what you can do with it. I’m not amazing at making my programs look good but they work and that’s what counts. I’ve already made a Blackjack game, a drinking game and Wout, Joeri and me also made a game last year where you had to click all the buttons in time to win . I don’t see myself as an expert, rather someone who loves programming and is eager to learn more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I manage to graduate college the next few years and get a job in IT I would be very happy. Networking is not really my thing because I can’t be as creative with it as I can be with programming, so I prefer a job where I can sit down and program all day. Some people think that’s is boring but I don’t see it that way. I get great satisfaction when I try to make something work and it finally does.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can’t even imagine what I would do if I didn’t have my computer. I use it for school, talking to friends, looking things up, playing videogames and much more. I can say IT has become an important part of my life because I just can’t live without it. It’s an ever-growing, fascinating world that I want to keep exploring!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;../../Bgysen.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>